<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ManualBashing - Notes and thoughts of Manuel Batsching</title><link>https://manualbashing.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on ManualBashing - Notes and thoughts of Manuel Batsching</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://manualbashing.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to restore or purge soft-deleted Azure API management services</title><link>https://manualbashing.github.io/post/2022-02-10-soft-deleted-apim/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://manualbashing.github.io/post/2022-02-10-soft-deleted-apim/</guid><description>Starting with REST API version, 2020-06-01-preview , Microsoft introduced the soft-delete feature to API Management service (APIM) (See: Azure API Management soft-delete (preview) | Microsoft Docs)
Deleting an APIM using the REST API version 2020-06-01-preview or higher will not obliterate the service but put it into the soft-delete state. It can be restored or purged (deleted forever) from this state. If nothing is done, the APIM will purge itself after a specific time.</description></item><item><title>dotnet build would fail for an angular app if nodejs were installed using asdf</title><link>https://manualbashing.github.io/post/2021-06-24-dotnet-build-fails-for-angular-app-if-nodejs-was-installed-using-asdf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://manualbashing.github.io/post/2021-06-24-dotnet-build-fails-for-angular-app-if-nodejs-was-installed-using-asdf/</guid><description>I was creating a new angular project using a template via dotnet cli today:
dotnet new angular Id did not have Node.js installed, so I installed it using asdf:
asdf plugin add nodejs asdf install nodejs latest This successfully installed Node.js v16.4.0. But when I tried to build the example project using dotnet build, I ran into the following error:
❯ dotnet build Microsoft (R) Build Engine version 16.7.2+b60ddb6f4 for .</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://manualbashing.github.io/about-page/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://manualbashing.github.io/about-page/</guid><description>Hi! My name is Manuel.
I currently work as an Application Developer and DevOps Engineer at abtis GmbH in Pforzheim, Germany.
This blog is (mostly) dedicated to technical topics topics that I deal with professionally, like:
PowerShell Infrastructure as Code Microsoft Azure Kubernetes If you like what I am doing here, follow me on twitter and let me know!</description></item></channel></rss>